vanillawowhunter.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy - Vanilla Wow Hunter - Guide, Addons, Macros, Pets

## Data We Collect

At Vanilla Wow Hunter, we will do are best to ensure any data we recieve from you will be secure. Your information will never be disclosed to a third party company.

  In addition, we use third party software, installed on the site, that collects personal and/or non personal information.

## Server Logs

IX Webhosting is hosting this website and may collect non personal information in their server logs: hour of connection, IP address, page requests, etc. Logs are kept for one year.  

## Traffic Monitoring

We monitor our traffic with Google Analytics. It consist in a javascript program, executed by your browser, that collect different types of non personal information and sends them to Google. Traffic statistics are then drawn from the collected data. Collected types of information include:  
Internet browser type and version;  
previously browsed page (where you came to the site from);  
hour of connection;  
number of pages seen;  
time spent on each page;  
etc.  

## Advertisement

Google Adsense handles all the advertising on our website. They may use information (not including your name, address email address, or telephone number) about your visits to Vanilla Wow Hunter and other Web sites in order to provide you with ads that you may be interested in.  

## Google Adsense

Proper serves Google premium ads on Vanilla Wow Hunter. Google makes use of cookies to track your habits and collect information about you (including personal information) when you navigate websites owned by Google or on which Google software is executed (such as the present site), in order to serve you what they deem to be the most appropriate ads.  
We have no control over the type of information collected by Google. For more information, please visit the Advertising and Privacy page from Google. This page also explains how to opt out of Google advertising cookies.  

## Cookies

Cookies may be used on Vanilla Wow Hunter for registration, traffic analysis, and advertisement purposes.  

## Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.  

## Further Information

For enquiries regarding our privacy policy, please get in touch with us at info@vanillawowhunter.com
